morning periscope aye
so all the Aeons are going to the post
office today we were up late putting
them in boxes and flashing them for you
guys so I'll show you the room and the
mayhem from the flash
big charging stations we can roll eons
have a bit of a charge and these are the
13 or just only 11 this is how many we
have left over these are the ones that
will be coming on the self-driving car
awareness to us I hope these ones are
well so these are 128 KB yawns I'm gonna
turn you guys sideways oh look at this
it's the Eon car eel your new copilot
getting started with Eon mount connect
drive
you'll find this right at the top set
this aside nice piece of high quality
foam we bought a lot of these foams and
a lot of them are not high quality you
guys know I'm very good quality I try my
best so you take this foam away and this
is what you guys will find the charger
and cable bag and the charger and cable
bag to charges this is the e on wall
charger and this is the e on car charger
now of course you don't actually need a
car charger you can also just put into a
panda the tenders would actually better
charge in this one Oh different type of
charger for around the world
you got us chargers bros it's a USB any
any USB charger kind of works too much
plastic it's not so much plastic so
these are young mounts notice that we've
pre-applied the backing sticky for this
you're just gonna stick that on your
windshield or wherever you want about
Ariane um it includes a sim removal kit
then we on of course has an LTE radio as
well as a Wi-Fi radio shipper plus does
not require LTE open pathos and this is
the allen wrench and we included a
second mount and if you look on the side
of the mount can see right here
maybe yeah it's really hard to see on
the camera but it says 28 on it and
that's because it's a 28 degree mount
meaning this limb at your realitor 28
degree angle if you have a higher car
like a rav4 you're gonna probably want
something like this the default mount
that comes on the EON itself which we're
gonna open up right and then this in
here is the yard so that is a completed
128 gigabyte young see the eight screws
on it so this is that 22 degree mount
that I was talking about and down here
we have the USB connector the heatsink
camera pretty nice decent build quality
there's no screen protector nope so
that's powered up see what ya
so something on will come charge some of
them will come mass charge let's hope
this one's a bit charged so you'll see
that it comes up with a comma no no no
we love finished and we are friends with
all regulatory agencies this is not a
self-driving car yet this is of course a
dashcam development kit you can install
whatever you'd like on it but when it
comes with his dash cam software called
shiver Plus which is open source on her
github so so welcome to Ian before we
get on the road let's cover some details
and connect to the internet
um so I'm not actually gonna set this
Jana up because I'm gonna box it back up
but that is what the EON unboxing
experience will look like any questions
so yeah I mean you know I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna ruin it for you by
clicking setup theory I knew you guys
would experience the adventure with you
get your own eon you want to buy it that
it's available for sale at shop.com ADAT
a I it's not a pre-sale actually oh if
you ordered an eon before yesterday it
is actually going to the post office
today it's already in a box and kind of
see a few of them over there that's just
part of the big mess of eons
is there an EOS for yes and that's what
them installed on the Aeons right now
seriously right here it says there's no
sim no car looks like it's got about a
20% charge oh we don't sell self-driving
I talk to my life seller presentation
about how soft driving is a journey and
not a destination the text isn't at the
point where we want enthusiasts using it
maava consumers
yeah kind of where we are unboxing yo
your new co father and that's what
shift+ looks like it's running we were
supporting now some people would wear
get support we have supporting all
support a common tire well that's a neo
unboxing thanks for joining